Any characters, actions, places, organizations, professions and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only. They are not intended to guide or encourage any behavior in the story. Viewer discretion is advised.
جميع الشخصيات والأحداث والأماكن والمنظمات والمهن والأحداث في هذه السلسلة خيالية وُضعت لأغراض الترفيه فقط. لا يُقصد بها توجيه أو تشجيع أي سلوك في القصة. يُرجى مراعاة تقدير المشاهد.
Yot.
ينام.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
What the fuck are you doing?
ماذا تفعل بحق الجحيم؟
Why the fuck are you grabbing my junk!?
لماذا بحق الجحيم تقوم بالاستيلاء على خردتي؟
Yot.
ينام.
I...
أنا...
You shouldn't have crossed my line like that, M.
لا ينبغي لك أن تتخطى حدودي بهذه الطريقة، يا سيدي.
I've always trusted you.
لقد وثقت بك دائمًا.
You are my most beloved friend.
أنت صديقي الحبيب.
So why the fuck would you do this shitty shit to me, you bastard!?
فلماذا إذن تفعل بي هذا الشيء القذر أيها الوغد؟
Yot.
ينام.
It wasn't my intention.
لم يكن هذا قصدي.
I wasn't in my right mind.
لم أكن في عقلي الصحيح.
From now on, I don't know if I can trust you, M!
من الآن فصاعدا، لا أعلم إذا كان بإمكاني أن أثق بك، يا م!
Yot.
ينام.
Yot. I'm sorry.
يوت. أنا آسف.
Get out!
اخرج!
Get out of my house!
اخرج من منزلي!
Go die wherever you want, you fucking bastard!
إذهب وموت أينما تريد، أيها الوغد اللعين!
What the hell is that noise?
ما هذا الضجيج؟
Shit!
اللعنة!
Get out of my house!
اخرج من منزلي!
Go die wherever you want, you fucking bastard!
إذهب وموت أينما تريد، أيها الوغد اللعين!
Yot.
ينام.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
M.
م.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Do you still dare to stay here?
هل لازلت تجرؤ على البقاء هنا؟
Huh!?
هاه!؟
Get up!
استيقظ!
So you're not going?
إذن أنت لا تذهب؟
You really gonna stay?
هل ستبقى حقا؟
M!
م!
Yot!
ينام!
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Will you follow M?
هل ستتبع م؟
Fuck it!
اللعنة عليك!
I don't care where he goes to die.
لا يهمني أين يذهب ليموت.
But...
لكن...
If you want, just follow him, Arm.
إذا كنت تريد فقط اتبعه، أرم.
I won't go!
لن اذهب!
Get out of the way!
ابتعد عن الطريق!
Bring me alcohol, Arm!
أحضر لي الكحول، يا آرم!
But... Yot.
الصنم... استلقي.
Alcohol. Go get it for me.
الكحول. اذهب واحضره لي.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Your incense.
بخوركم.
Please come this way.
من فضلك تعال من هنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Say goodbye to him for the last time.
قل له وداعا للمرة الأخيرة.
I'm sorry for your loss.
أنا آسف لخسارتك.
I never imagined he'd leave us this early.
لم أتخيل أبدًا أنه سيتركنا في وقت مبكر كهذا.
Thank you for coming to my son's funeral.
شكرا لكم على حضوركم جنازة ابني.
I'm sorry for your loss.
أنا آسف لخسارتك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
What? Why did you kick the door?
ماذا؟ لماذا ركلت الباب؟
Jiji. What are you doing here?
جيجي. ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I'll take a shower and go back to M's funeral.
سأستحم وأعود إلى جنازة م.
Why did you come back? What about the others?
لماذا عدتَ؟ ماذا عن الآخرين؟
Yeah. I'm tired, so I'll come back first.
نعم. أنا متعب، لذلك سأعود أولاً.
Yot, are you okay?
يوت، هل أنت بخير؟
Yeah.
نعم.
So... since you're tired...
إذن... بما أنك متعب...
Would you like to take a shower together?
هل ترغب في الاستحمام معًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
Come on, babe.
هيا يا حبيبتي.
Yot.
ينام.
Don't rush me.
لا تستعجلني.
Slowly.
ببطء.
We still need to go out.
لا زال يتعين علينا الخروج.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Huh? Yot.
هاه؟ يوت.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Jiji, continue taking a shower.
جيجي، استمر في الاستحمام.
I'm not in the mood anymore.
أنا لم أعد في مزاج جيد بعد الآن.
What?
ماذا؟
What's wrong with him?
ما به؟
M.
م.
I'm your brother.
انا أخوك.
Don't haunt me.
لا تطاردني.
Damn it...
عليك اللعنة...
Hey! Fuck! What is that?
هيه! اللعنة! ما هذا؟
M.
م.
I'm your brother.
انا أخوك.
Don't haunt me.
لا تطاردني.
Don't forget that I'm your brother.
لا تنسى أنني أخوك.
Reverend Father!
أيها الأب الموقر!
What? You're so loud.
ماذا؟ صوتك مرتفع جدًا.
I think, should we change our route?
أعتقد، هل يجب علينا تغيير مسارنا؟
Huh? Why?
هاه؟ لماذا؟
It's nothing much, but how about we change our path once in a while?
إنه ليس شيئًا مهمًا، ولكن ماذا لو قمنا بتغيير مسارنا من حين لآخر؟
Why do you want to change our route today?
لماذا تريد تغيير مسارنا اليوم؟
Just go along our normal route.
فقط اذهب على طول طريقنا الطبيعي.
This is the usual route where people wait to give alms.
هذا هو الطريق المعتاد الذي ينتظر فيه الناس لإعطاء الصدقات.
Why did you stop walking, Reverend Father?
لماذا توقفت عن المشي يا أبانا القسيس؟
You may not even realize what you're doing.
ربما لا تدرك حتى ما تفعله.
Are you talking to me, Reverend Father?
هل تتحدث معي يا أبانا القسيس؟
I'm helping you with the alms round.
أنا أساعدك في جولة الصدقات.
But now, you and your friend are in different realms.
لكن الآن، أنت وصديقك في عالمين مختلفين.
It's better if we go our separate ways.
من الأفضل أن نذهب في طرقنا المنفصلة.
Please don't tease me, Reverend Father.
من فضلك لا تضايقني، أيها الأب القس.
If not, I won't wait for you anymore.
إذا لم يكن كذلك، فلن أنتظرك بعد الآن.
I'm leaving now, Reverend Father.
سأغادر الآن، أيها الأب القس.
The more you resist my words,
كلما قاومت كلماتي،
the burden of sin will grow heavier upon you.
سيصبح عبء الخطيئة ثقيلاً عليك.
That's my final warning.
هذا تحذيري الأخير.
Let humans be with humans,
فليكن البشر مع البشر،
and ghosts with ghosts.
والأشباح مع الأشباح.
What the hell is this?
ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
It's a cold packs.
إنها كمادات باردة.
Did you grow up without knowing what a cold pack was?
هل نشأت دون أن تعرف ما هي الكمادة الباردة؟
Not like that.
ليس هكذا.
I mean, why did you do this to me?
أعني، لماذا فعلت هذا بي؟
Have you ever seen a nurse wiping the doctor's sweat during surgery?
هل سبق وأن رأيت ممرضة تمسح عرق الطبيب أثناء إجراء عملية جراحية؟
Yes, it's exactly like that.
نعم، إنه مثل ذلك تمامًا.
I've seen you repair a lot of cars,
لقد رأيتك تقوم بإصلاح الكثير من السيارات،
I'm worried you're getting exhausted.
أنا قلق من أنك مرهق.
Many thanks, Mr. nurse.
شكرا جزيلا لك يا سيد الممرضة.
Shit.
اللعنة.
I feel like I'm becoming more like a proper adult.
أشعر وكأنني أصبحت شخصًا بالغًا بشكل صحيح.
Mr. nurse.
السيد الممرضة.
Come to think of it,
إذا فكرت في الأمر،
why don't you consider studying this?
لماذا لا تفكر في دراسة هذا؟
It suits you.
إنه يناسبك.
Why?
لماذا؟
Or is it because...
أم أن السبب هو...
I gave you first aid after you fight with those out-of-town bikers?
هل قدمت لك الإسعافات الأولية بعد قتالك مع هؤلاء الدراجين من خارج المدينة؟
And you are the loser.
وأنت الخاسر
Loser my ass!
الخاسر مؤخرتي!
They ganged up on me.
لقد اجتمعوا ضدي.
Looking back, it was worth it,
بالنظر إلى الماضي، كان الأمر يستحق ذلك،
because I got to date Jiji.
لأنني حصلت على موعد مع جيجي.
Uh, M.
اه، م.
Thank you so much for always being by my side.
شكرا جزيلا لكونك بجانبي دائما.
If it weren't for you, I might've died on the side of the street?
لو لم تكن أنت، ربما كنت مت على جانب الشارع؟
You? Die on the street?
انت؟ تموت في الشارع؟
You're Yot.
أنت يوت.
Top dog in every damn league.
أفضل كلب في كل الدوريات اللعينة.
Hey, you're just insulting me with that last part.
مهلا، أنت فقط تهينني بهذا الجزء الأخير.
Damn.
اللعنة.
Damn, you just low-key insulting me?
لعنة، هل أنت فقط تهينني بطريقة غير مباشرة؟
You wanna fight me now?
هل تريد قتالي الآن؟
You wanna fight me?
هل تريد القتال معي؟
Yot!
ينام!
You guys are so ungrateful.
أنتم غير شاكرين جدًا.
You won't even touch the trash.
لن تلمس حتى القمامة.
Look.
ينظر.
Yot!
ينام!
Son!
ابن!
Oh. Are you working?
أوه، هل تعمل؟
It's good that you're working.
من الجيد أنك تعمل.
But seriously, what's wrong with you?
ولكن بجدية، ما الخطأ معك؟
Your friend just died, and you're not even going to his funeral?
لقد مات صديقك للتو، وأنت حتى لا تذهب إلى جنازته؟
Why are you so angry at him?
لماذا أنت غاضبة منه هكذا؟
Don't blame me if your friend haunts you later.
لا تلومني إذا كان صديقك يطاردك لاحقًا.
Huh?
هاه؟
Aren't you going to answer me?
ألا تريد أن تجيبني؟
I'm confused.
أنا مرتبك.
Annoying.
مزعج.
Then I'll go see my friend.
ثم سأذهب لرؤية صديقي.
Hey, rain, don't fall again!
يا مطر لا تسقط مرة أخرى!
I didn't bring an umbrella with me.
لم أحضر معي مظلة.
What do I do if I get wet?
ماذا أفعل إذا تبللت؟
Hello, handsome.
مرحباً أيها الوسيم.
Are you here?
هل أنت هنا؟
I came to get my car. Oh.
جئت لأخذ سيارتي. أوه.
I mean, CUM to get my car.
أعني، تعال للحصول على سيارتي.
Aren't you there?
هل انت لست هناك؟
Oh.
أوه.
You're down there, right?
أنت هناك، أليس كذلك؟
Need a hand fixing your undercarriage?
هل تحتاج إلى مساعدة في إصلاح الهيكل السفلي الخاص بك؟
Okay, you didn't answer me.
حسنًا، لم تجيبني.
You're ignoring me. Playing hard to get.
أنت تتجاهلني، وتتظاهر بأنك صعب المنال.
I'll help you.
سأساعدك.
Right now?
الآن؟
Okay, right now.
حسناً، الآن.
1...
1...
2...
2...
3!
3!
What the hell is that?
ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟
Shit!
اللعنة!
- Fuck!
- اللعنة!
Fuck! Fucking shit!
اللعنة! اللعنة!
Shit.
اللعنة.
What the hell are you talking about, Arm?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه يا آرم؟
Ghosts don't exist.
الأشباح غير موجودة.
Just try to show up,
فقط حاول أن تظهر
I'll kick his face so hard he'll forget he's even a ghost.
سأركل وجهه بقوة حتى ينسى أنه شبح.
Gosh, Yot.
يا إلهي، يوت.
Hold on till I'm get back, then you can call the ghost out.
انتظر حتى أعود، وبعدها يمكنك استدعاء الشبح.
Man, you...
يا رجل، أنت...
So why did you come back home?
فلماذا عدت إلى المنزل؟
Your mom told me to come get you.
والدتك قالت لي أن آتي لأخذك.
You didn't go to M's funeral yesterday, did you?
لم تذهب إلى جنازة M أمس، أليس كذلك؟
But I already went yesterday.
لكنني ذهبت بالفعل بالأمس.
But you didn't step inside.
ولكنك لم تدخل إلى الداخل.
Maybe...
ربما...
the reason why M is haunting everyone like this
السبب وراء مطاردة M للجميع بهذه الطريقة
is that he still has unresolved worries.
أنه لا يزال لديه مخاوف لم يتم حلها.
Worried about what?
قلق بشأن ماذا؟
Or...
أو...
he's worried you won't get into university.
إنه قلق بشأن عدم قبولك في الجامعة.
Why does M have to worry about my university studies?
لماذا يجب على م أن يقلق بشأن دراستي الجامعية؟
Honestly, you know better than anyone
بصراحة، أنت تعرف أفضل من أي شخص آخر
how much M worries about...
كم يقلق م...
About...
عن...
About the promise you made to him!
عن الوعد الذي قطعته له!
What the hell promise is that?
ما هو هذا الوعد الجحيم؟
The promise you made to ordain for me.
الوعد الذي قطعته لترسيمي.
Hey!
يا!
Hey...
يا...
Why're you screaming?
لماذا تصرخ؟
Sorry.
آسف.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Nothing at all.
لا شيء على الإطلاق.
Head to the temple first,
توجه إلى المعبد أولاً،
I'll follow after I finish showering.
سأتبعك بعد أن أنتهي من الاستحمام.
Okay, then...
حسنا إذن...
See you at the temple.
نراكم في المعبد.
I'd better head out quickly.
من الأفضل أن أخرج بسرعة.
Where did all the people go?
أين ذهب كل هؤلاء الناس؟
It's so quiet.
إنه هادئ جداً.
Hey, look at this pavilion.
مهلا، انظر إلى هذا الجناح.
There aren't many people here.
ليس هناك الكثير من الناس هنا.
So quiet.
هادئ جداً.
Don't joke around.
لا تمزح.
They just brought a body in here.
لقد أحضروا للتو جثة إلى هنا.
Just happened.
لقد حدث للتو.
Did you know everyone around here's been haunted?
هل تعلم أن الجميع هنا مسكونون؟
They've been haunted even during the daytime.
لقد كانوا مسكونين حتى في النهار.
Not surprise.
ليس مفاجئا.
Not many people came to the funeral.
لم يحضر الجنازة الكثير من الناس.
Umm, you're right.
اممم، أنت على حق.
When someone dies in such an unlucky way, it's probably hard to be reborn.
عندما يموت شخص بهذه الطريقة المؤسفة، فمن الصعب أن يولد من جديد.
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Be careful, he might come and haunting your ass.
كن حذرا، قد يأتي ويطارد مؤخرتك.
Ugh, I got goosebumps.
آه، لقد أصبت بالقشعريرة.
Ugh, I'm heading back now.
أوه، أنا متجه إلى الخلف الآن.
M, what about you?
م ماذا عنك؟
Do you want a Western wife or a Thai wife?
هل تريد زوجة غربية أم زوجة تايلاندية؟
M likes petite, fair-skinned, Asian-type girls.
يحب M الفتيات الصغيرات، ذوات البشرة الفاتحة، والآسيويات.
No matter where she's from, he's okay as long as she's fair-skinned and looks Asian.
بغض النظر عن المكان الذي أتت منه، فهو بخير طالما كانت ذات بشرة بيضاء وتبدو آسيوية.
Yot.
ينام.
How the hell do you know my type?
كيف بحق الجحيم تعرف نوعي؟
Don't be embarrassed.
لا تشعر بالخجل.
- Hey.
- مهلا.
Looking at porn pics?
هل تنظر إلى صور إباحية؟
Is he your type?
هل هو نوعك المفضل؟
Huh?
هاه؟
M!
م!
You.
أنت.
Alright, listen.
حسنا، استمع.
I...
أنا...
Stop!
قف!
Why didn't you tell me this is your type?
لماذا لم تخبرني أن هذا هو نوعك؟
Hey.
يا.
I think your body kinda pretty similar to this.
أعتقد أن جسمك مشابه إلى حد ما لهذا.
Mom, this is what girls are liking these days.
أمي، هذا ما تحبه الفتيات هذه الأيام.
Didn't you promise you'd ordain for me?
ألم تعدني بأنك سترسمني؟
Shit!
اللعنة!
Yot.
ينام.
Please open the door.
من فضلك افتح الباب.
Are you jerking off in there?
هل أنت تستمني هناك؟
Hurry up, I'm going to bed.
اسرعي سأذهب إلى السرير.
Jerk M!
أحمق م!
Stop haunting me.
توقف عن مطاردتي.
You're fucking dead!
أنت ميت تماما!
What the fuck do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بحق الجحيم؟
If I were dead, would I be standing right here?
لو كنت ميتًا، هل كنت سأقف هنا؟
You're really dead.
لقد مت حقا.
And now you're a ghost haunting me like this.
والآن أنت شبح يطاردني هكذا.
What did you promise me?
ماذا وعدتني؟
I was just saying that!
كنت أقول ذلك فقط!
I didn't think you'd actually fucking die.
لم أكن أعتقد أنك ستموت فعليًا.
I was just kidding!
لقد كنت أمزح فقط!
I don't actually want to ordain!
أنا لا أريد أن أقوم بالرسامة فعليا!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Damn.
اللعنة.
M.
م.
Yot.
ينام.
Mom, help me!
أمي ساعديني!
- What's wrong? - M's ghost, Mom!
- ماذا حدث؟ - شبح م، أمي!
- M's ghost! - Not a ghost!
- شبح م! - ليس شبحًا!
M's ghost!
شبح م!
Get a grip!
سيطر على الموقف!
- M's ghost! - Yot!
- شبح م! - يوت!
M's ghost is haunting me, Mom!
شبح م يطاردني يا أمي!
Yot.
ينام.
Yot!
ينام!
Get a grip!
سيطر على الموقف!
I was still talking to him just now, Mom.
كنت لا أزال أتحدث معه للتو، يا أمي.
M's ghost!
شبح م!
Yot.
ينام.
No, it isn't.
لا، ليس كذلك.
What happened to your face?
ماذا حدث لوجهك؟
I'm okay, forget it.
أنا بخير، انسي الأمر.
Mom.
أم.
I said, what happened to your face?
قلت ماذا حدث لوجهك؟
Did the loan sharks hurt you?
هل أضر بك المقرضون؟
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Yot.
ينام.
Listen.
يستمع.
I won't let myself lose anything else.
لن أسمح لنفسي بخسارة أي شيء آخر.
Mom
أم
will protect you.
سوف يحميك.
About ordaining,
عن الرسامة،
if you're not willing,
إذا لم تكن راغبًا،
then you don't have to.
إذاً لن تحتاج إلى ذلك.
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
Mom.
أم.
I've made up my mind.
لقد اتخذت قراري.
I've decided.
لقد قررت.
I will be ordained.
سوف يتم ترسيمى.
Yot.
ينام.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
I may not be a perfect mother,
ربما لا أكون أمًا مثالية،
but this mother
ولكن هذه الأم
will always love you.
سوف احبك دائما.
Yot.
ينام.
I love you, my son.
انا احبك يا ابني.
I'm sorry for the past.
أنا آسف على الماضي.
Can you forgive me?
هل يمكنك أن تسامحني؟
- I love you, Yot. - Me too, Mom... I’m sorry.
- أنا أحبك يا يوت. - وأنا أيضًا يا أمي... أنا آسف.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm sorry, son.
انا آسف يا ابني.
[We'll never leave each other, my best friend]
[لن نترك بعضنا البعض أبدًا، يا صديقي المفضل]
Jerk M.
جيرك م.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I didn't think it would turn out like this.
لم أكن أعتقد أن الأمر سيصبح بهذا الشكل.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Please forgive me, M.
أرجوك أن تسامحني يا سيدي.
Esāhaṃ bhante,
Es??ha??? bhante,
suci-ra-panibri.
suci-ra-panibri.
Suci-ra-parinibbūtam pi,
Suci-ra-parinibb??tam pi,
dhammañ ca, bhikkhusaṅghañ ca,
داما؟؟ كاليفورنيا، بهيكوسا؟؟؟غا؟؟ كاليفورنيا,
Bhikkhusaṅghañ ca,
Bhikkhusa???gha?? ca,
Nail.
مسمار.
Body hair.
شعر الجسم.
Hair.
شعر.
Suci-ra-parinibbūtam pi,
Suci-ra-parinibb??tam pi,
taṃ bhagavaṃ...
ta??? bhagava???...
Bhagavaṃdaṃ.
بهاجافا???دا???.
Saraṇaṃ gacchāmi.
Sara???a??? gacch??mi.
Esāhaṃ bhante.
Es??ha??? bhante.
Suci-ra-parinib.
سوسي-را-بارينيب.
Pa...
حسنًا...
Parinibbūtam pi.
Parinibb??tam pi.
Gacchāmi.
جاكش؟؟مي.
Dhammañ ca, bhikkhusaṅghañ ca,
داما؟؟ كاليفورنيا، بهيكوسا؟؟؟غا؟؟ كاليفورنيا,
labheyyāhaṃ bhante,
لابهيي؟؟ها؟؟؟ سيدي الجليل،
tassa bhagavato,
ضريبة البهاجافاتو
dhammavina ye pabbajjāṃ,
ما اسم الباباج؟؟؟؟؟؟,
labheyaṃ upasaṃpadaṃ.
labheya??? upasa???pada???.
On the occasion of your ordination today,
بمناسبة رسامتك اليوم،
you must seek your mother's forgiveness.
يجب عليك أن تطلب المغفرة من والدتك.
I respectfully bid farewell as I go forth into ordination.
أود أن أقول وداعًا بكل احترام وأنا أتجه نحو الرسامة.
If I have ever done anything wrong to you,
إذا فعلت أي شيء خاطئ معك،
whether to your face or behind your back,
سواء على وجهك أو خلف ظهرك،
I sincerely ask for your forgiveness.
أطلب منك الصفح بصدق.
May this ordination go as I have intended.
أتمنى أن تسير هذه الرسامة كما أردتها.
Yes.
نعم.
I always forgive you, Yot.
أنا أسامحك دائمًا، يوت.
I'm sorry, Mom.
انا آسف يا أمي.
I was never truly mad at you.
لم أكن غاضبًا منك أبدًا.
Please be diligent in your monastic studies.
يرجى أن تكون مجتهدًا في دراساتك الرهبانية.
Okay?
تمام؟
Son.
ابن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I never thought this day would come.
لم أكن أتوقع أن يأتي هذا اليوم.
Do your best with the ordination, my dear.
أبذل قصارى جهدك في الرسامة يا عزيزتي.
Okay?
تمام؟
Put your heart into studying the Dhamma.
ضع قلبك في دراسة الدارما.
♫ Wishing you luck from now on ♫
??? أتمنى لك التوفيق من الآن فصاعدا ???
♫ Stay strong and don't let sorrow take hold ♫
??? ابقى قويا ولا تدع الحزن يسيطر عليك ???
♫ Take good care of yourself ♫
??? اعتني بنفسك جيدا ???
♫ I'm alright, ♫
???أنا بخير، ???
♫ not leaving your side ♫
???لا يترك جانبك ???
♫ Just wishing you sweet dreams from now on ♫
??? أتمنى لك أحلامًا سعيدة من الآن فصاعدًا ???
♫ Just the two of us know ♫
??? فقط نحن الاثنين نعرف ???
♫ When you feel lonely, ♫
??? عندما تشعر بالوحدة، ???
♫ I'll stand by you, whether happiness or sadness ♫
سأقف بجانبك سواء في السعادة أو الحزن
♫ Please don’t cry, though fate pulled us apart too soon ♫
من فضلك لا تبكي، على الرغم من أن القدر فرقنا بسرعة كبيرة.
In my life,
في حياتي،
other than my dad's garage,
باستثناء مرآب والدي،
I only have you
انا فقط لدي انت
as my safe zone.
كمنطقتي الآمنة.
Please bless me.
من فضلك باركني.
Yathā vārivahā pūrā. Paripūrenti sāgaraṁ.
يث؟؟ v؟؟ريفاه؟؟ ص؟؟ص؟؟. باريب؟؟رينتي ق؟؟جارا؟؟؟.
Evameva ito dinnaṁ.
هل هذه إيفاميفا أيضًا؟؟؟
Petānaṁ upakappati.
يوم الجمعة هو يوم upakappati.
Icchitaṁ patthitaṁ tumhaṁ.
إيتشيتا؟؟؟ باثيتا؟؟؟ تومها؟؟؟.
Khippameva samijjhatu.
Khippameva samijjhatu.
Sabbe pūrentu saṅkappā.
لأن الوالدين آمنين.
Cando paṇṇaraso yathā.
Cando pa??????araso yath??.
Maṇi jotiraso yathā.
Ma???i jotiraso yath??.
I'm going to order some equipment. Do you want anything?
سأطلب بعض المعدات. هل تريد شيئًا؟
Huh?
هاه؟
I need one battery.
أحتاج إلى بطارية واحدة.
Battery, right?
البطارية، أليس كذلك؟
Fan and serpentine belt too.
المروحة والحزام الثعباني أيضا.
Fan...
معجب...
Serpentine belt...
حزام أفعواني...
Okay, sure.
حسنا، بالتأكيد.
This month's income is pretty good.
الدخل هذا الشهر جيد جدًا.
3...
3...
Client's arrived.
لقد وصل العميل.
Yot.
ينام.
Let's break up.
دعونا ننفصل.
I don't think we're compatible.
لا أعتقد أننا متوافقين.
Uh.
أوه.
He is Nont.
إنه نونت.
My new husband.
زوجي الجديد.
- Nont. - Yes.
- لا. - نعم.
Let's go. It's hot.
هيا بنا. إنه حار.
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
As I expected.
كما توقعت.
She changes men every time.
إنها تغير الرجال في كل مرة.
Jeez, she's showing off her new man.
يا إلهي، إنها تظهر رجلها الجديد.
Jeez, showing off a luxury car.
يا إلهي، إظهار سيارة فاخرة.
That's supposed to be luxury?
هل من المفترض أن يكون هذا ترفًا؟
I could buy it if I wanted to.
أستطيع شراءه إذا أردت ذلك.
Just ignore her, Mom.
فقط تجاهليها يا أمي.
Okay, I'll ignore her.
حسنًا، سأتجاهلها.
I wish her to get a good husband and be rich as she wants.
أتمنى لها أن تحصل على زوج صالح وتكون غنية كما تريد.
Let's focus on our work.
دعونا نركز على عملنا.
Is this all you need?
هل هذا كل ما تحتاجه؟
- Yes. - Would you like anything else?
- نعم. - هل تريد شيئا آخر؟
No, Mom. It's okay now.
لا يا أمي، لا بأس الآن.
- Damn! What the fuck!? - Hey, what?
- اللعنة! ماذا بحق الجحيم؟ - مهلا، ماذا؟
You startled me.
لقد فاجأتني.
Huh?
هاه؟
There was no one in the car just now, right, Mom?
لم يكن هناك أحد في السيارة للتو، أليس كذلك يا أمي؟
The car was shaking.
وكانت السيارة تهتز.
That car hood was about to break my neck.
كان غطاء السيارة على وشك أن يكسر رقبتي.
No.
لا.
There were only the two of us at the garage today.
كنا فقط اثنين في المرآب اليوم.
Arm isn't here, is he?
الذراع ليس هنا، أليس كذلك؟
Arm went to see Reverend Father since morning.
ذهب آرم لرؤية الأب القس منذ الصباح.
I heard he's going to university or something.
سمعت أنه سيذهب إلى الجامعة أو شيء من هذا القبيل.
I'll wait and see how long he can stay focused.
سأنتظر وأرى إلى متى سيتمكن من البقاء مركزًا.
Don't overthink it.
لا تفكر كثيرا في الأمر.
Okay.
تمام.
♫ At least even though we are apart, we still got to know each other ♫
على الأقل حتى لو كنا منفصلين، ما زلنا نتعرف على بعضنا البعض ؟؟؟
[We'll never leave each other, my best friend] ["I will wait for the day you come back"]
[لن نترك بعضنا البعض أبدًا، يا صديقي العزيز] ["سأنتظر اليوم الذي تعود فيه"]
♫ This is all I can give you as a gift ♫
هذا كل ما أستطيع أن أقدمه لك كهدية
[We'll never leave each other, my best friend] ["I will wait for the day you come back"]
[لن نترك بعضنا البعض أبدًا، يا صديقي العزيز] ["سأنتظر اليوم الذي تعود فيه"]